avegasguide.com 2014-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Las Vegas show tickets, Cheap Las Vegas hotels and more - avegasguide.com

This Privacy policy owner sets our practices with respect to the collection, use plus disclosure of personal information in connection with www.AVegasGuide.com (the Site). This Privacy policy owner may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us plus an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact plus demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarized form.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We may disclose certain personal information as follows:  
\- by publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers  
\- to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf,  
\- to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or  
\- to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.  
Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.

**Cookies and IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to identify you & your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, & administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools & to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. they use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests & to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. They also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer. They use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While they use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, & they do not have access to this information.

**Links**

This Site contains links to other web-sites, such as web-sites providing national search capabilities & information resources designed to inform buyers & sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. they are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.  Ensure you review the privacy policies of the web-sites that you visit.

**Security**

We protect against the loss, misuse & adjustment of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the web may be intercepted by unknown third parties.

**Corrections/Contact**

Users of this Site may contact AVegasGuide.com to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, & we will take necessary measure/s to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, contact us at Sales@AnalyzedMedia.com
